你就会被深深吸引的
you would get hooked.
我是说 在你空闲时你会做什么超级酷炫的事啊
I mean, what is it that you do in your free time that's so cool?
修理古董车然后卖给名人
Fix up old cars and sell them to celebrities.
汤姆·哈迪 英国演员 代表作
这是我为什么会认识汤姆·哈迪
That's why I'm friends with Tom Hardy.
好吧 所以我们同意我们都一样酷
Right, so we agree that we're all equally cool.
我们到了 这是Parlov那组的座谈会
Here we go. This is Parlov's panel.
"幻想作品写作中的多样性"
"Diversity in Fantasy Writing."
6号房间幻想作品写作中的多样性
哦 排队的到我后面去
Ooh, the line starts here.
还真是很多样化的多样性座谈会啊
Real diverse diversity panel.
然后 人们总是问我
And, like, people always ask me,
"你是从哪里得到的灵感呢"
"Where do you get your ideas?"
老实说 是从维基百科上
And honestly, Wikipedia.
我总是试图从生活中取得灵感
I always try to pull from life.
Tiffany女王 是我以之前遇见的一位可爱的女主人的名字命名的
Queen Tiffany, of course, was named after a lovely hostess
她住在佛罗里达州博尼塔温泉市
that I met in Bonita Springs in Florida.
你知道 我总是想自己写上一本书
You know, I've always wanted to write a book myself,
但是我只知道警察的事
but all I know about is cops,